





ABOUT ME

Full-stack software developer focusing on JavaScript technologies, most notably React, Redux, Angular, Node, is, Express and Koa. Skilled in Linux administration, Bash scripting, MongoDB, PostgreSQL and Redis. Seasoned remote worker experienced in managing geographically distributed teams.

EXPERIENCE

2020 Full-Stack Developer Hey DJ is a web app that performs tracklist recognition in DJ sets using the ACRCloud music recognition API. You give it a recorded DJ set, it returns a list of tracks that the DJ played. I have built the whole application from the ground up and subsequently received a funding offer to get it into production, which is currently planned for Q3 2020. React / Node.js / Express / MongoDB / Mongoose / FFmpeg / ACRCloud 2020 Full-Stack Developer Fitvid Tracker Fitvid Tracker is a web app that helps users organize personal workout plans based on YouTube videos. I have worked on this project as a member of a 4-person team. My contribution was implementing an API client to connect front-end to the back-end, the scheduling system, Google authentication, Redux state management, and a significant portion of the front-end logic. React / Redux / Node.js / Koa / MongoDB / Mongoose / Material UI 2016 - 2019 **Engineering Program Manager** Red Hat Managed the planning, development and delivery of 20+ releases of various Red Hat products. Agile / Scrum / Kanban / JIRA / Linux / Java / JBoss / 3scale 2015 **Documentation Program Manager** Red Hat Managed a team of technical writers responsible for documentation of various Red Hat products. Agile / Scrum / Linux / Java / JBoss / DocBook / AsciiDoc 2014 - 2015 **Content Strategist Red Hat** Provided strategic guidance in documentation planning for various Red Hat products. Linux / Java / JBoss / DocBook / AsciiDoc **Technical Writer** 2012 - 2014 **Red Hat** Authored and maintained documentation of various Red Hat products. Linux / Java / JBoss / DocBook / AsciiDoc 2008 - 2012 **Technical Writer Kentico Software** Authored and maintained product documentation of Kentico CMS.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Codeworks, Barcelona, Catalonia, ES Immersive software engineering bootcamp focused on full-stack JavaScript.

Master's Degree in Applied Informatics Faculty of Informatics, Masaryk University, Brno, CZ Study field Service Science, Management and Engineering.

Bachelor's Degree in Applied Informatics Faculty of Informatics, Masaryk University, Brno, CZ Study field Applied Informatics.

ASP.NET / C# / MS SQL Server / HTML / CSS

CERTIFICATIONS

Certified ScrumMaster (CSM) Red Hat Certified System Administrator Certificate of Proficiency in English

LANGUAGES

English - proficient (C2) German - basic (A2) Czech - native

CURRENT CAREER GOAL

Gain experience and keep expanding my developer skill set with new technologies.